[{"id": 503, "question": "Now some women are spending a weekend at Mother's Camp . There, husbands and children are not allowed. Why would a woman want to take a vacation without her family? Some women say they need time to be alone. At Mother's Camp a woman has room to herself. She can sleep, read or watch TV, and no one will bother her. No children will ask,\"Mom, what's for dinner?\" No husband will say, \"Oh, dear, I can't find any clean socks.\"In fact almost 50% of women in the United States work outside the home. Many of them work full-time and then come home to a second job-taking care of their homes and families. These working women say one of their biggest problems is housework. In the United States, working wives do about 75% of the housework. Many of their husbands say they want to help. But then they burn ...\n\nQ: Why would some mothers like to be alone? Because_.", "options": ["they don't like their husbands and children", "they have to work full-time", "they are too busy to relax themselves", "they want a new life"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1961, "question": "Every year, Americans send millions of tons of food to the landfill . What if you could use all of those rotten vegetables to heat your home? That's happening in one unlikely laboratory: the Newtown Creek Wastewater Treatment Plan in Brooklyn The plant's longtime manager, Jimmy Pynn, shows off the plant's crown jewels: eight huge, shiny, oval-shaped steel tanks known as digester eggs. Each one contains millions of gallons of black material that's roughly pea soup. Pynn calls it \"black gold\". \"The digesters like to be fed like us: three times a day,\" he says. \"They like to be kept warm, 98 degrees. And that's what we have these guys for: to make methane ,which can be used to heat homes or make electricity.\" Right now, what these bacteria are digesting is mostly sewage mud. But they are bein...\n\nQ: According to MacBride, what's the problem for New York City?", "options": ["Its rapid development causes environmental problems.", "Its system of separate out food scraps is complex.", "It fails to pay enough attention to recycling.", "It has too much amount of waste."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1100, "question": "Hilton English Language Center Information for New Students CLASS TIME: 8:30a.m.--10:00a.m., 10:30a.m.--12:00a.m., 1:30p.m.--3:00p.m.. The Language Center is open Monday to Friday. Each class has one afternoon free per week. On the first day, go to the lecture hall to check your timetable. SELF-ACCESS: The language laboratory (Room 1110) is open Monday to Friday from 3:15p.m. to 5:00p.m. for all full-time students. You can learn how to use computers for language games or word-processing . There are tapes for students to borrow to practice their English. Go in and ask the teacher to show you. If you plan to take public examinations, there are dictation and listening comprehension tapes for you to practice with. There are cloze exercises on the computers. Ask your class teacher for a list of...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE?", "options": ["No teachers are in the language lab.", "90% attendance is required for the students.", "Books can't be taken out of the center.", "Students can prepare for exams by listening to tapes."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 585, "question": "Some mothers in Senegal are learning a new way to save the lives of babies born too soon. The idea is borrowed from the way mother kangaroos carry their young in front in a pouch. The baby kangaroo stays in this built-in baby carrier until it can survive independently. Kangaroo mother care is also known as the skin-to-skin method for premature babies. The direct contact with the mother keeps the baby warm. It also lets the baby breastfeed at any time. The mother's heartbeat also helps control the baby's breathing rate. Every year, seven thousand babies are born at the health center where Ousmane Ndiaye works in Guediaway, outside Dakar. One in five is underweight. But Senegal has few incubators in which to keep premature babies warm. In Africa, one newborn in twenty dies. A major reason is...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT the advantage of the kangaroo method?", "options": ["The babies can get warmth from their mothers", "It is convenient for mothers to feed their babies", "The direct skin contact reduce the risk of failing ill", "The mother's heartbeat helps the baby breathe normally"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2485, "question": "A good friend of mine was complaining about her son the other day.\"Did you notice,\" she started, \"how he didn't wait for me to get my salad before he dove into his?\" True enough, the boy attacked his plate faster than a cat in the wild.Without manners, we're no more than animals.Actually, that's not true.I've been watching and feeding a group of wild cats, and they show unusual politeness toward each other.Even when food is _ , they take turns, leaving at least a small part for the next in line. My mother educated her three children to have good manners all the time.We were made to feel very uncomfortable as if we were sitting on pins and needles until we got used to saying please, thank you, pardon me, and I'm sorry.And I have to say, while it was a painful learning experience, it was one...\n\nQ: We learn that the writer's mother   _  .", "options": ["was strict about her children's manners", "never punished her children", "had beautiful blue eyes", "was not good at singing"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 351, "question": "Forget Twitter and Facebook, Google and the Kindle. Television is still the most influential medium around. Indeed, for many of the poorest regions of the world, it remains the next big thing--finally becomes globally available. And that is a good thing, because the TV revolution is changing lives for the better. Across the developing world, around 45% of families had a TV in 1995; by 2005 the number had climbed above 60% . That is some way behind the U.S. ,where there are more TVs than people, and where people now easily get access to the Internet. Five million more families in sub-Saharan Africa will get a TV over the next five years. In 2005 , after the fall of the Taliban ,which had banned TV, I in 5 Afghans had one. The global total is another 150 million by 2013--pushing the numbers ...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["TV Will Rule the World", "TV Will Disturb the World", "TV Will Better the World", "TV Will Remain in World"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2072, "question": "Five-year-old Jocelyn Rojas spent all day playing happily with her friends outside her grandmother's apartment building. Her mom, Jaimee, kept her eye on the little girl from a window. At about 4 p.m., Jocelyn walked around the corner of the building to get her bicycle. However, half an hour later, she disappeared. Jaimee called 911. A short time later, police officers and firefighters crowded inthe area, blocking streets and searching the neighborhood. Officers handed out photos of the girl wearing thick-framed glasses. Temar Boggs, 15, a school athlete in track, was with some friends moving a couch into the apartment of his elderly neighbor when one officer approached him and asked if he'd seen Jocelyn. Unfortunately, none of them had seen her. A little bit later, Temar and his friends w...\n\nQ: From what Neil Harkins says, we can know   _  .", "options": ["Temar and his friends did a heroic thing.", "Temar is a boy with little courage.", "The kidnapper was under control because of Temar and his friends.", "Temar didn't want to catch people's attention."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2448, "question": "PEOPLE who have had a painful experience may wish they could wipe the memory from their minds. Researchers at Johns Hopkins University, US, say that this may someday be possible. A drug remains far off, but researchers have laid a foundation with their discovery that proteins can be removed from the brain's fear center to cut memories forever. Previous research had already shown that a special behavior therapy could cut painful memories. But relapse was possible because the memory hadn't necessarily disappeared. By looking at that process, Richard Huganir and Roger Clem, two researchers from Johns Hopkins University, discovered a \"window of vulnerability \" when proteins are created. The proteins help signals travel within the brain as painful memories are made. Because the proteins are uns...\n\nQ: What is Kate Farinholt's opinion of the research?", "options": ["People may lose the chance to learn from their bad experiences.", "The research will be a great breakthrough in treating painful memories.", "People could suffer long-term memory loss.", "People could forget happy memories as well."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 225, "question": "He looked like a pirate. With his handkerchief tied in a knot behind his little nine-year-old head, he looked like a pirate, a sad pirate. The first time little David came to our camp, he was hairless and worn out from medical treatments. He was also very angry. Paul Newman's camp counselors ( ) were hoping to fill David's days with fun and laughter. But David stayed inside himself, wanting to be alone, or in a corner of the cabin. At this camp for children with life-threatening illnesses, we had seen some pretty tough children worn out by cancer recover full of energy despite their illness. But we saw little progress in David no matter what we tried with him. Five days into the eight-day session saw a quiet, sad little pirate. Then something happened on that fifth night. Something at camp...\n\nQ: The camp counselors failed to fill David's beginning days with fun and laughter, mainly because David  _  .", "options": ["behaved like a pirate", "remained in a bad mood", "was left alone at the camp", "was teased by other campers"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3057, "question": "Trapped on the 37thFloor Melinda Skaar wasn't expecting any phone calls. Skaar was working late in her office at the First Internet bank of California. By 10:45 that night she was almost ready to go home when the phone rang. Picking it up, she heard a guard shouting. There is a fire! Get out of there. Skaar didn't panic. She figured that it was just a small fire. Her office building was huge. There were 62 floors and her desk was on the 37thfloor. Skaar called out to office mate Stephen Oksas, who also stayed late to work. But when they got out to the hallway, they were met by a cloud of black smoke. Rushing back, Skaar shut the door and filled the space at the bottom of the door with her jacket to keep the smoke out. Then they called 911. before they could call their families, however, th...\n\nQ: The first sentence of the passage is to  _  .", "options": ["introduce Skaar", "get the reader's attention", "explain the cause of the event", "tell the background information"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2154, "question": "The Haitian tsunami gave scientists a chance to find out how well vital and potentially life-saving warning systems were working. Noaa's Pacific Marine Environmental Laboratory has developed a warning system that picks up signals of tsunamis directly from the sea-floor. It is called Dart-the Deep-ocean Assessment and Reporting of Tsunamis. If seismometers detect an earthquake, the Dart buoys will determine what is happening to sea levels, and whether a big wave might be on the way. This information is then sent via satellite to a central location which can organize an alarm. Within 50 minutes of the Haiti earthquake, this system was able to issue an alarm to other countries in the Caribbean to say that a small tsunami had been caused to start, and that was unlikely to affect them. Dr Berna...\n\nQ: In which section would you probably read the passage in a newspaper?", "options": ["Education and Society", "Culture and Leisure", "Science and Technology", "Health and Medicine"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3471, "question": "The story goes that some time ago,a man punished his 3-year-old daughter for wasting a roll of gold wrapping paper.Money was tight and he became infuriated when the child tried to decorate a box to put under the Christmas tree.Nevertheless,the little girl brought the gift to her father the next morning and said,\"This is for you,Daddy.\" The man was embarrassed by his earlier overreaction,but his anger flared again when he found out the box was empty.He yelled at her,stating,\"Don't you know,when you give someone a present,there is supposed to be something inside?\" The little girl looked up at him with tears in her eyes and cried,\"Oh,Daddy,it's not empty at all.I blew kisses into the box.They are all for you,Daddy.\" The father was crushed.He put his arms around his little girl,and he begged f...\n\nQ: What's inside the box according to the little girl?", "options": ["Nothing.", "Air.", "Kisses.", "Gold wrapping paper."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 317, "question": "Cutting global warming pollution would not only make the planet healthier, it would make people healthier too, new research suggested. Cutting carbon dioxide emissions could save millions of lives, mostly by reducing preventable deaths from heart and lung diseases, according to studies released Wednesday and published in a special issue of The Lancet, a British medical journal. \"Relying on fossil fuels leads to unhealthy lifestyles, increasing our chances of getting sick and in some cases takes years from our lives,\" US Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen Sebelius said in a telecast briefing from her home state of Kansas. \"As greenhouse gas emissions go down, so do deaths from cardiovascular and respiratory diseases. This is not a small effect.\" Instead of looking at the health il...\n\nQ: What does the passage mainly talk about?   _  .", "options": ["How can people live longer?", "Cutting carbon dioxide emissions saves lives.", "Global warming threatens people's lives.", "People should stop relying on fossil fuels."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2804, "question": "Child labor -- the employment of children in industry, often against their will -- has been a problem for many years. Over a hundred years ago, Charles Dickens shocked many of his readers when he described the conditions under which young children worked in British factories. The conditions Dickens described continue almost unchanged today in many parts of the world. The only difference is that today employment of children is confined(limited)to small industries and family businesses, such as hotels, restaurants and particularly farms, rather than to large factories. Girls suffer more from child labor practices than boys. Many of them are forced to start work when they are only ten years old. Although the work they are given to do is often light, it is often harmful to the health. Recently...\n\nQ: To solve the problem of child labor, the writer suggests the following BUT   _  .", "options": ["looking over factories more closely", "raising their payment and improving the system of education", "improving laws of protecting children's interests", "punishing lawbreakers with severer fines"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3288, "question": "From a very early age, some children show better self-control than others. Now, a new study that began with about 1,000 children in New Zealand has tracked how a child's low self-control can predict poor health, money troubles and even a criminal record in their adult years. Researchers have been studying this group of children for decades now. They observed the level of self-control the youngsters displayed. Parents, teachers, even the kids themselves, scored the youngsters on measures like \"acting before thinking\" and \"Persistence in reaching goals.\" The study led by Moffitt of Duke University and colleagues followed 1,000 children from birth to age 32 in Dunedin, New Zealand. \"The children who had the lowest self-control when they were age three to ten, later on had the most health prob...\n\nQ: According to Moffitt,_.", "options": ["only good genetic factors can shape their lives in the future", "scientists know well why some children have better self-control", "self-control in childhood has nothing to do with criminal activity", "willpower as a child really influences people's chances of adulthood"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 401, "question": "prefix = st1 /PITTSBURGH, Sept. 7 -- At 26, many people haven't even decided on a career. Luke Ravenstahl, cashing in on his family's political tradition, is already the mayor of Pittsburgh, the youngest mayor of any major city in the country. Although mayors elsewhere have been younger, Jeff Dunkel was 18 in 2001 when he was elected mayor of Mount Carbon, small towns inNew York, and elsewhere have also elected teenagers as mayors. But,Tallahassee, is the only other city with a population over 100,000 that has had a mayor as young as Mr. Ravenstahl. A supporter of Mr. Ravenstahl said concerns about Mr. Ravenstahl's age would _ once the city saw his work ethic. But now comes the hard part. As he strives to be taken seriously and take charge of a city only recently back from the brink of ban...\n\nQ: What can you infer from the article about Pittsburgh?", "options": ["It is a small town in New Yorkfamous for steel mills.", "It has always enjoyed prosperous economic success.", "Many young college students there are the new hope of the district.", "It is a major city in the U.S.A with a population slightly smaller than 100,000."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3054, "question": "One warm September night, Mira had come down to the beach to enjoy the night air. She closed her eyes and listened to the waves. Suddenly, she could hear another sound, so she opened her eyes and looked down at the sand. It was moving! All of a sudden she could see a tiny head coming out. Then a turtle appeared! One by one they struggled out of their underground nests. Mira looked in surprise at the baby turtles. Mira knew the turtles should head towards the waves and swim away, so she was puzzled when they began to pull themselves towards the dunes . Suddenly, she remembered something her grandmother had told her. \"Sea turtles bury their eggs on the beach every year in April and in September. Those baby turtles hatch and head back down to the sea. But some of them never make it. Sometimes...\n\nQ: Why did Mira run to her house?", "options": ["To get a flashlight", "To turn off the porch light.", "To communicate with her parents.", "To ask her grandmother about the lights."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1270, "question": "Spring is the time to go out and enjoy the weather and scenery.Here are some events to attend in March of 2012 in Oregon! Oregon Country Fair(OCF), 9 am to 7 pm on March 8 - 10 OCF first started in 1969, and it's blossomed into an outstanding example of what a non - profit should be. OCF is an event of shopping & atmosphere, and food ranging from Indian & Afghani cuisine to Italian & France cuisine.Wonderful craft & music never stop.From the time you get there until the time you leave, everyone has a smile on their faces, and they wave and say hello.For tickets, go and visit www.Oregoncountryfair.org. 30thAnnual Seaside Beach Volleyball Tournament, 8 am to 6 pm on March 12 - 14 The Annual Seaside Beach Volleyball Tournament is an amateur tournament that draws amateur volleyball players to ...\n\nQ: OCF covers the following EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["music", "dishes", "dance", "artworks"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1417, "question": "Water is the most common substance found on the earth, but less than 1% of the earth's water is suitable for drinking. More than 1,000,000,000 people around the world survive on just over 1 galon of water a day. Probebly more than 3,000,000,000 people may suffer from not having enough water by the year 2025. You are considered lucky if you live in a country where you can drink water out of your kitchen tap or bathroom tap. People in some countries have to pay for drinking water at home. So clean water is one of our most valuabe natural resources . In fact, peole waste so much clean water today. In factories lots of water is wasted. At home many people are not taking showers but still baths, and many are brushing their teeth with the tap turned on. Children are no longer taught how to save ...\n\nQ: People are ecouraged to use rainwater   _  .", "options": ["so that is can make our life easier", "so that clean water can be kept for other uses", "because is it free and easy to get", "because there is no claen water left for them"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2319, "question": "Where and how you eat are just as important as what you eat. Take this test to find your eating style to make sure you're getting the nutrition you need. Which statements sound like you? Group 1: # I like to make my plate look pretty before I dig in for the first bite. # I often help my parents make recipes. # I could win the first prize in the \"World's Slowest Eater\" contest. Group 2: # The crumbs in the sofa are mine -- I eat while watching TV. # I can finish a whole box of snacks quickly while I'm doing something else. # Sometimes I'm surprised to find my plate empty. Where did all the food go? Group 3: # Sometimes I eat my dinner standing up. # I spend more time in the drive-through than at the dinner table. # Breakfast? Who has time for breakfast? If you answered mostly Group 1: You e...\n\nQ: If Tom answered mostly Group 2, which advice will you give him?", "options": ["Place healthy snacks at hand while doing homework.", "Hold a ball in his hand while watching TV.", "Eat high-fat foods slowly and carefully.", "Help his parents make recipes now and then."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1637, "question": "One day a student went to see his teacher. He had been given an important position and now was coming to say goodbye to his teacher. The old man asked him how he would live among high officials. The student answered, \" I will be all right. I have prepared a hundred high hats, one for each official I will meet. I am sure I will succeed.\" The teacher got angry on hearing this. \"What?\" he cried. \"Is this what ten years of my teaching has made of you? Nothing but flatterer ?\" \"Excuse me, honored master,\" the student rose to his feet and apologized hurriedly. \"But you have always been absorbed in your studies and don't know how vulgar the world has come to be. There are few men in the world who are above flatterers like you.\" \"There is something true in what you said,\" the teacher nodded, smili...\n\nQ: The phrase \"rose to his feet\" means  _  .", "options": ["stood up", "kicked with his feet", "became quite excited", "raised his feet"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 840, "question": "Individuality is the particular character, or aggregate (total) of qualities that distinguishes one person or thing from others. Many artists late in the last century were in search of a means to express their individuality. Modern dance was one of the ways some of these people sought to free their creative spirit. At the beginning there was no exacting technique, no foundation from which to build. In later years, trial, error and genius founded the techniques and the principles of the movement. Eventually, innovators even drew from what they considered the dread ballet, but first they had to get rid of all that was academic so that the new could be discovered. The beginnings of modern dance were happening before Isadora Duncan, but she was the first person to bring the new dance to genera...\n\nQ: Compared to those of the ballet, Isadora Duncan's costumes were less   _  .", "options": ["costly", "colorful", "graceful", "restrictive"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1931, "question": "Most people believe they don't have imagination. They are wrong. Everyone has imagination, but most of us,once we became adults, forget how to access it. Creativity isn't always connected with great works of art or ideas. People at work and in their free time routinely think of creative ways to solve problems. Maybe you have a goal to achieve,a tricky question to answer or you just want to expand your mind! Here are three techniques to help you. This technique involves taking unrelated ideas and trying to find links between them. First,think about the problem you have to solve or the job you need to do. Then find an image,word,idea or object,for example,a candle. Write down all the ideas/words associated with candles:light,fire,matches, wax,night,silence,etc. Think of as many as you can. T...\n\nQ: We learn from the third technique that a good salesman should ask himself \"   _   ?\".", "options": ["what do I usually do", "what did my boss tell me to do", "what are my customers' needs", "how should I sell my products"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2349, "question": "Centerville High School Essay Contest \"Write All About It\" Calling All Aspiring Authors--Centerville High School Essay Contest *Rules 1.Students are asked to present essays of 500 to 700 words of their own work. Any essay containing material plagiarized from another source will be disqualified . 2.Manuscripts should be typed double-spaced,with the student's name,address,and grade level on a separate sheet of paper. 3.Essays must be turned in by 4:00 p.m. on November 30.They can be brought to Mrs. Elton in Rom 104 or to Mr. Markham in the school library. *Essay-Writing Tips 1.Catch your readers' interests--Your opening should immediately pull your readers into your essay. Asking a question or starting with an story,quotation,or surprising statement is a good way to do this. 2.Create a pictu...\n\nQ: The first writing tip given is mostly about  _  .", "options": ["the use of quotations and stories in an essay", "using active verbs and lively adjectives", "how a student should begin an essay", "how to submit your essays"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 457, "question": "A thief who dropped a winning lottery ticket at the scene of his crime has been given a lesson in honesty. His victim, who picked up the ticket, then claimed the PS25000 prize, managed to trace him, and handed over the cash. The robbery happened when maths professor Vinicio Sabbatucci,58, was changing a tyre on an Italian motorway. Another motorist, who stopped \"to help\", stole a suitcase from his car and drove off. The professor found the dropped ticket and put it in his pocket before driving home to Ascoli in eastern Italy. Next day, he saw the lottery results on TV and, taking out the ticket, realized it was a winner. He claimed the 60 million lire prize. Then he began a battle with his conscience. Finally, he decided he could not keep the money despite having been robbed. He advertised...\n\nQ: The underlind word \"spurning\" in the last sentence can be replaced by   _  .", "options": ["accepting", "rejecting", "claiming", "canceling"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2748, "question": "Many of you may wonder what else to do besides watching TV or surfing the Internet on weekends.Why not have a picnic? Junior 2 students at Beijing No.4 Middle Schoo1 had a \"King of cooking\" competition* Earlier this month,about 300 students at the schoo1 went to a suburb of Beijing to have the contest.They were divided into 24 groups.Each group had buyers,slicers ,firemakers.washers and cooks. Firemakers faced the most problems during the time.Some of them had no idea how to keep fire burning. \"The fire kept going out.we had to blow at the sparks and put on corn leaves and old newspapers,\"said Wu Mofei,13. \"It took us an hour to make the fire.Our eyes had tears from all the smoke and our faces became dirty,\"he added. When the fires were finally made,the cooks became the busiest people.Huan...\n\nQ: According to the passage,we can know  _  .", "options": ["only ten students were titled \"King of Cooking\" in this competition", "the \"King of Cooking\" competition has been held once every year in the past six years", "Wang Xiaoyue was titled a \"King of Cooking\" in this competition", "Beijing No.4 Middle School has been encouraging students to take part in all kinds of competitions"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3384, "question": "Life is too short to waste a moment, so while you still have time, let your hair down, remove that \"boring\" tag in your so-called life and start making it worthwhile. Below are some tips that will help you live a wonderful life. 1. Keep a Positive Attitude. Enjoy what you have and work on getting the things you desire. Psychologists believe that optimism is a good defense against unhappiness, so it is better to keep your optimism alive. Feeling sad about your life will only make you sadder, so be happy. 2. Don't Be Afraid to Take Risks. Life is all about taking risks, and that's the exciting part of it. Challenges and failure are part of life. Once you learn how to take risks, you'll soon realize how good it feels not to let moments pass you by. 3. You only have one life, so make it worthw...\n\nQ: From Tip One we know that we should   _   .", "options": ["never be afraid to take risks", "try something new every day", "focus on the good things in life", "get rid of all our former habits"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3458, "question": "I was with a group of businessmen, and we were dealing with a question--What is a good person? At a certain point during the discussion, one of the students--a young man of about thirty--described an event that happened at Christmas. He and his five-year-old son were decorating the Christmas tree, and a little boy came to the front door begging. If you ever visit Mexico, you will see that the people there take begging as nothing to get upset about and nothing to get embarrassed by. So, this little boy came to the door, a boy about the same age as my student's son. The father and the son went to the front door, and the father went back with his five-year-old son and said to him, \"Give him one of your toys.\" At the words, the little boy quickly picked up some toy, and his father said to him,...\n\nQ: The sentence \"can I do that again?\" showed that the boy   _  .", "options": ["got pleasure by helping the little beggar", "wanted to please his father", "began to like the little beggar", "wanted to be the little beggar's friend"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 53, "question": "\"What is the most important thing you've done in your life?\" The question was put to me during a presentation I gave to a group of lawyers. The answer came to me in an instant. It's not the one I gave, because the situation was not right. As a lawyer in the entertainment industry, I knew the audience wanted to hear some amusing stories about my work with well-known people, but here's the true answer: The most important thing I've ever done occurred on October 8,1990. I began the day playing tennis with an old friend I hadn't seen for a while. Between points we talked about what had been happening in each other's lives. He and his wife had just had a baby boy, who was keeping them up at night. While we were playing, a car came screaming up the road toward the courts. It was my friend's fath...\n\nQ: Which of the following is conveyed in this story?", "options": ["Family and relatives can not take the place of friends.", "More people are a great comfort when one is in trouble.", "It is best to be here when someone needs you.", "You can certainly help a friend if you want to."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 712, "question": "Your Car Is Ready for Take-off The flying car has been talked about for many years,but now it appears that the idea is about to become a reality. An international company has built a two-seater plane that, at the touch of a button ,transforms into a car perfectly suitable for driving on public roads. It has been designed so that the wings fold up automatically; and it takes just 15 seconds to switch between flying and driving. With its wings fully open and the propeller spinning, it can take off from any airfield. Flying cars are quicker than traditional ones for travelling from city to city,and they can run on ordinary fuel. Another big advantage is that they are cool ,like something you would see in an action film. At the moment9however, the flying car's wheels are illegal to leave the g...\n\nQ: The flying car is presently forbidden to take off because  _  .", "options": ["many people think driving it not very safe", "it's hard to decide whether it's a car or a plane", "the government and the authorities don't accept it", "there are still some technical problems to be solved"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1090, "question": "What does the word \"home\" mean to you? How do you say the word in French? In Spanish? In your language? Although people usually know what the word means, it often has no exact translation. It's not surprising really, because the idea of home differs from country to country, and from person to person. A home is more than a roof and four walls. It's the cooking, eating, talking, playing and family living that go on inside, which are important as well. And at home you usually feel safe and relaxed. But it's not just that homes look different in different countries, they also contain different things and reveal different attitudes and needs. For example, in cold northern Europe, there's a fire in the living room or kitchen and all the chairs face it. In the south, where the sun shines a lot an...\n\nQ: Which one is true according to the passage?", "options": ["People in Britain seldom have balconies because it's so hot outside.", "\"Home\" is a place where you feel safe and relaxed.", "Although homes look different in different countries, they have the same needs.", "Houses in northern Europe always have big windows and cool stone floors."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 460, "question": "High school announcements Do you have a high school announcement to make? Are you hosting a high school sports event or tournament? Are you looking for a coach? Let us know, and we'll share it with \"Tribune\" readers. August 21---- Sacred Heart is looking for two assistant baseball coaches immediately. Practices and games are held after school at 3:30 pm. Some experience in playing or coaching is preferred. If interested, e-mail Ron Schwartz at ramsad1@aol.com. August 7 ----- Loyola Academy will host its 12th Rambler Baseball Winter Workshop for students in fourth through eighth grades on Aug. 26. the early registration fee is $70 and registration at the door is $85. contact Loyola coach Bill San Hamel at 847-920-2523 to register early. July 17 ----- St. Patrick will host a Youth Holiday Ba...\n\nQ: Which of the following high schools wants to have a match?", "options": ["Sacred Heart.", "The Marist.", "Bartlett.", "hinsdale."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 176, "question": "A gentleman put an advertisement in a newspaper for a boy to work in his office. Out of the nearly fifty men who come to apply, the man selected one and dismissed the others. \"I should like to know,\" said a friend, \"the reason you preferred that boy, who brought not a single letter--not a recommendation ,\" \"You are wrong\" said the gentleman. He had a great man. He wiped his feet at the door and closed the door after him, indicating that he was careful. He gave his seat immediately to that old man, showing that he was kind and thoughtful. He took off his cap when he came in and answered my questions, showing that he was polite and gentlemanly. \" All the rest stepped over the book which I had purposely put on the floor.\" He picked it up and placed it on the table; and he waited quietly for h...\n\nQ: The gentleman dismissed the other boys because  _  .", "options": ["they didn't pick up the book lying on the floor", "they pushed and crowded", "they were impolite", "all the above"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1307, "question": "To a large degree, the measure of our peace of mind is determined by how much we are able to live in the present moment. Regardless of what happened yesterday or last year, and what may or may not happen tomorrow, the present moment is where you are -- always! We allow past problems and future concerns to control our present moments, so much that we end up anxious, frustrated, depressed, and hopeless. We often convince ourselves future will be better than today. John Lennon once said, \"Life is what's happening while we're busy making other plans. \"When we're busy making other plans\", our children are busy growing up, the people we love are moving away and dying, our bodies are getting out of shape, and our dreams are slipping away. In short, we miss out on life. Many people live as if life...\n\nQ: \"Many people live as if life were a dress rehearsal\" suggests that   _  .", "options": ["they always wish to be an actor or an actress", "they believe that their present life is well prepared for their future", "they are always busy making plans for future", "They all have a guarantee that they will be alive tomorrow"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2056, "question": "From the same place that brought you the Robot Suit HAL comes the \"motorized knee\".Designed by researchers at Japan's Tsukuba University, the device supports the flex( ) of the knee, which enables a runner to use 30% less muscle power compared to running unassisted. Coming in a kit , the device consists of a small motor that helps flex the knee, a sensor that detects the knees' degree of flex, and a safety lever --all of which attach to the user's leg.The user is also forced to carry a backpack that holds a control unit and battery to power the motor.All up the device weighs around 5kg,which will probably lessen the performance benefits of wearing the device somewhat.In experiments runners wearing the device could jog at 7.5kmh, which is hardly anything special--but predictably they could ...\n\nQ: Which of the following aspects of the device is NOT mentioned in the passage?", "options": ["Its advantages.", "Its components.", "Its weight.", "Its price."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1047, "question": "Cyberspace, the connections between computers in different places, considered as a real place where information, messages and pictures exist, mirrors the real world in many ways. People ask for information, play games, and share hobbies. Others buy and sell products. Still others look for friendship, or even love. Unlike the real world, however, your knowledge about a person is limited to words on a computer screen. Identity and appearance mean very little in cyberspace. Rather, a person's thoughts--or at least the thoughts they type--are what really count. So even the shyest person can become a chat room star. Usually, this \"faceless\" communication doesn't create problems. Identity doesn't really matter when you're in a chat room discussing politics or hobbies. In fact, this emphasis(,) o...\n\nQ: According to the passage, chatting in the cyberspace   _  .", "options": ["puts emphasis on people's thoughts", "needs people to be rich in knowledge", "stresses more about people's identity", "allows people to discuss politics secretly"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3247, "question": "Italy is one country where beauty is prized more than any other virtue. That is, except in the small town of Piobbico, the self-declared World Capital of Ugly People. The road sign at the edge of the town even warns visitors that they are entering the ugly zone. People who consider themselves ugly have been gathering in Piobbico since the 1960s. That's when Ugly Club president Telesforo Lacobelli established a dating agency for women who believed they were too ugly to attract husbands. Lacobelli believes that he is ugly himself because he has a short nose in a country where long or large noses have always been considered beautiful. People from around the world travel to Piobbico to tell their sad stories of ugliness. During the annual Festival of the Ugly, which occurs on the first Sunday ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true according to the passage?", "options": ["Ugly people are most respected in Italy.", "The Festival of the Ugly is held every two years.", "Ugly people are unfairly treated in society.", "The uglier one is, the better life he or she lives."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1255, "question": "Yang Qunhui, 28, a graduate of Chengdu University of Information Technology, Sichuan Province, gave up her job with a monthly salary of 20,000 yuan ($3,014) at a famous company, but has started her own restroom-ad business with five other graduates, becoming a \"restroom queen.\" The company, opened in May, is now the only one of its kind in Chengdu. It has two goals: to find suitable restrooms to place ads and to find clients who are willing to put their ads in them. \"We are now trying to find restrooms to place the ads. A larger area means more ad sources,\" said Yang. Yang got the idea to run the company one year ago when she looked for toilet repairing information on the Internet but finally noticed companies in Beijing and Shanghai doing restroom ads. \"It's so interesting,\" she said. \"Ev...\n\nQ: According to the passage , which of the following is true?", "options": ["Yang accepted a job with a monthly salary of 20,000 yuan instead of starting her own restroom-ad business.", "Yang opened the company as soon as she graduated from Chengdu University of Information Technology.", "The restroom-ad company that was opened by five graduates is now the only one of its kind in Chengdu.", "One of the company's goals is to find clients who are willing to put their ads in the restrooms."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2934, "question": "Scientists estimate that more than 60 percent of cancer deaths in the United States are preventable through lifestyle changes. Although there is no certain way to avoid all cancers, reducing individual risk factors greatly decreases the likelihood of getting many forms of this dangerous disease. The American Chemical Society estimates that smoking causes nearly 30 percent of all cancer deaths in the United States -- that is, about 166,000 cancer deaths each year. All cancer deaths caused by tobacco smoking could be prevented completely by not smoking and not using smokeless tobacco. For those who already smoke, quitting will reduce the risk of developing cancer. Studies show that after about ten years of not smoking, a past smoker's risk lowers to about the level of those who have never sm...\n\nQ: What kind of people increase their chances of getting cancers?", "options": ["Those whose foods contain less sugar, animal fat, and salt.", "Those who are not moderate in drinking, smoking or eating.", "Those who have only one or two drinks regularly per day.", "Those whose diet contains little red meat and a lot of vegetables."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2554, "question": "Bernie was smart and wanted to be his own boss.When Bernie was 25 he took a wife. Bernie had saved some money and decided on a dry goods and grocery store combined. Marie had a knack for arranging the merchandise to appeal to customers and Bernie didn't mind the long hours. He was happy, and life was good.The business thrived until the great depression hit the entire country. No one had money to purchase pretty things or even food. In 1930, Marie had a heart attack and left Bernie alone. Following Marie's death, which Bernie felt was brought about from worrying about the store, He lost interest in everything. He had few customers and did not make them feel welcome, Bernie wandered about the store , dusting a bit and sweeping the floor. His inventory remained almost the same, as nothing muc...\n\nQ: According to Bernie , Marie's death is mainly because of   _  .", "options": ["the heart attack", "the position of the shop", "the hard work", "the worry about the store"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1604, "question": "Security Services advise that there have been robberies reported in the East Oxford area, carried out by a group and involving threats of and showing of a knife.The victims have all been young males of student age and appearance who have been walking alone between 7 pm and the early hours of the morning.Some of the victims have been followed from the O2 and the Regal Hotel. The Crime Prevention Advisor offers the following advice: *If possible walk home in a group, not on your own.If someone tries to take something from you by force, it may be best to give it to them, this way it will avoid you getting injured. *If someone tries to follow you, make for a public place, such as a shop or a restaurant or walk towards other people.Make lots of noise and use your personal alarm to shock the per...\n\nQ: The O2 is the name of   _  .", "options": ["a gas", "a stadium", "a city", "a magazine"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2998, "question": "With my hands and knees on the floor of the airplane, I was searching for an old lady's missing hearing aid during the flight from Sydney to Los Angeles. It occurred to me that this may not be the most dignified posture for a Buddhist nun . I had seen the old lady from the seat in front of me as she walked up and down the passage with a flashlight. I asked a few times what was wrong, but she didn't answer at first --- she couldn't hear me. She was wearing a woolen coat. Judging from her accent, she came from Eastern Europe. Do you know what hearing aids cost? Thousands, especially for the new tiny hidden-in-the-ear type she described. It takes a long time for an appointment to make a new one, and many doctor visits to get the thing adjusted right. Therefore, my dignity seemed less importan...\n\nQ: Where was the hearing aid found?", "options": ["On the previous flight.", "Close to the old lady' seat.", "On the wheelchair.", "In another jet cabin."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 439, "question": "You could feel sorry for Alberto Torres, who is blind. The last thing he remembers seeing was his daughter being born 13 years ago. Then the world went blank; he can only imagine what his only child looks like now, as a teenaged honor student. Bad luck is no stranger to this warm and thoughtful 37-year-old man. His mother died of cancer when he was 4, and his father, who was often ill, had to give him up to the care of the state when he was 11. He later worked for 19 years in a workshop making household goods, deathly boring work. Earlier this month, Alberto Torres's wife, who had just been laid off from her job, had to have a breast removed due to cancer and now faces a year of radiation treatments. Things seemed always to go from almost incredibly bad to worse. Even Mr. Torres's good luc...\n\nQ: Mr. Torres does not feel sorry for himselfbecause he   _  .", "options": ["was once saved by his lovely guide dog", "is taken good care of by the government", "thinks it's natural to have setbacks in life", "believes it takes a little longer to do things"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 411, "question": "Soon after you have your first child, the question of having a second one is raised by friends and family. However, as the pattern of having two children in a family is challenged by modern family units, there are a few reasons why it is not selfish to want only one child. Today, the role of women has changed a lot. But nowadays, a wife has to help her husband earn the bread and butter as well as well as looking after her family. In demanding times like these, a woman has to put in more physical and emotional effort than any other member of the family. Raising a child comes at a cost that remains only heard of, until you find yourself paying it. The good reality of double income with no kids suddenly comes crashing down when there is a child involved in the picture. When one parent (the mo...\n\nQ: What does the writer mainly want to tell us in the passage?", "options": ["It is not selfish to have only one child in a family.", "Raising a child costs a lot nowadays.", "It is more difficult to raise several children in a family.", "Women are playing a more important role in the family than before."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 704, "question": "\"The days when the management in Western companies presented gold watches to long-serving employees to thank them for loyal service is now just a memory.\" says the Educational and Training Support Agency. This new development in the shape and movement of the workforce throughout Western businesses is partly a result of the way that layers of middle management are being removed, leaving more workers responsible for their own development. \"Having workers take responsibility for their own development might be dramatic, but it is now the rule,\" says the Educational and Training Support Agency. \"Today, not only are workers more mobile, they have to run to keep up with changes.\" says the Government-founded agency.\"It is no longer enough for a worker to gain a set of skills.Workers need the abili...\n\nQ: Companies require their employee's development mainly because   _  .", "options": ["it will finally help to bring more profits to the company", "it can attract more workers who pay special attention to self-development", "it is good for the employees to develop their skills", "it will make workers more responsible and loyal to the company"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 714, "question": "Microblogging is a broadcast medium in the form of blogging. A microblog differs from a traditional blog in that its content is typically much smaller, in both actual size and aggregate file size. Microblogs \"allow users to exchange small elements of content such as short sentences, individual images, or video links\". As with traditional blogging, microbloggers post about topics ranging from the simple, such as \"what I'm doing right now,\" to the thematic , such as \"sports cars.\" Commercial microblogs also exist, to promote websites, services and/or products, and to promote collaboration within an organization. Some microblogging services offer features such as privacy settings, which allow users to control who can read their microblogs, or other ways of publishing rights besides entering t...\n\nQ: Why is a microblog different from a traditional blog?", "options": ["Because a microblog doesn't include pictures, but a traditional blog does.", "Because a microblog doesn't include videos, but a traditional blog does.", "Because a microblog has smaller contents than a traditional blog in actual and total file size.", "Because a microblog can only be written on the cell-phones."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3040, "question": "Welcome to Gold Coast Wax Museum HIGHLIGHTS The Gold Wax Museum is one of the Cold Coast's longest running attractions. It's a collection of famous figures. It's Australia's largest museum of its kind, featuring more than 110 life-size wax figures copies of British and Australian History. The Wax Museum is visited by many thousands of people each year who are shocked at the amazing realism of the life-size figures in authentic costumes. This is your invitation to wander through at your leisure and meet many important and famous people's figures on Queensland's Gold Coast. Come face to face with such celebrities as Michael Jackson, President Obama, past President John F. Kennedy, King Hussein, members of the Royal Family, and many others whose lives have all left an indelible mark on our wo...\n\nQ: If you visit the Gold Coast Wax Museum, you can", "options": ["see many members of the Royal Family in person in the Museum", "enjoy some world-class vivid max-works in the Museum", "meet many leading local and internatioanal sculptors in the Museum", "e at any time of the year except at Christmas Day"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1950, "question": "\"It was cool,because I got a chance to be in a studio and see how a record is made,\"says 14-year-old Javon Martin,who joined the music clubhouse 3 years ago.\"It has impacted my life in a big way. People are actually starting to see me as an artist.\"Ten-year-old Akheylah Hunter didn't play an instrument when she became a club member last year. Now,she plays piano and sings with the band. What she likes best,she says,is performing.\"We performed in different places,\"she says.\"We go on trips and it is fun.\" Since the Music Clubhouse opened three years ago,it's served almost 500 kids.Aggeler says performing in front of different audiences helps the young musicians build self-esteem.Coming to the club to prepare for those performances helps them learn how to deal with their personal problems and...\n\nQ: What is Mr.Aggeler's possible post?", "options": ["An organizer of the club.", "A conductor of the band.", "An expert in child problems.", "A parent of one of the children."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 758, "question": "Among various programs, TV talk shows have covered every inch of space on daytime television. But no two shows are more opposite in content, while at the same time standing out above the rest, than the Jerry Springer and Oprah Winfrey shows. Jerry Springer could easily be considered the king of \"rubbish talk\". The show takes the ever-common talk show titles of love, sex, cheating, and hate, to a different level. Clearly, the Jerry Springer show is about the dark side of society, yet people are willing to eat up the troubles of other people's lives. Like Jerry Springer, Oprah Winfrey takes the TV talk show to its top. But Oprah goes in the opposite direction. The show is mainly about the improvement of society and different quality of life. Contents are from teaching your children lessons, ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is likely to be a topic of the Oprah Winfrey show?", "options": ["A new type of robot.", "National hatred .", "Family income planning.", "Street accident."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1759, "question": "I'm part of the Roots & Shoots program founded by Dr. Jane Goodall. The program is intended to make and promote positive changes in the world. As Dr. Goodall says, \"What you do makes a difference, and you have to decide what kind of difference you want to make.\" In Bulgaria, where I live, homeless dogs are everywhere. Many people here turn a blind eye to them. But I cannot ignore the life of a street dog whenever I see one wandering in the street, looking for something to eat. That's why I'm no longer a food waster. When I see wasted food, I always think of a hungry dog climbing to garbage bins, searching for food that people have thrown there. When eating in a restaurant, I'm not afraid to take leftover food to feed stray cats or dogs. A week ago, I saw a homeless dog around the garbage b...\n\nQ: What can be concluded from the text?", "options": ["There are few homeless dogs where the author lives.", "The author takes homeless dogs home and raises them.", "Seeing homeless dogs makes the author never waste food.", "People throw food into garbage bins to feed homeless dogs."], "answer": 2}]